[
  {
    "_id": "111111111111111111111100",
    "username": "marina",
    "password": "password",
    "firstname": "Marina",
    "lastname": "Valiquette",
    "questions": [
      {
        "prompt": "A",
        "answer": "A",
        "next": "1"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "B",
        "answer": "B",
        "next": "2"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "C",
        "answer": "C",
        "next": "3"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "D",
        "answer": "D",
        "next": "4"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "E",
        "answer": "E"
      }
    ],
    "head": "0"
  },
  {
    "_id": "111111111111111111111101",
    "username": "jeffrey",
    "password": "password",
    "firstname": "Jeffrey",
    "lastname": "Mahmoudi",
    "questions": [
      {
        "prompt": "A",
        "answer": "A",
        "next": "1"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "B",
        "answer": "B",
        "next": "2"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "C",
        "answer": "C",
        "next": "3"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "D",
        "answer": "D",
        "next": "4"
      },
      {
        "prompt": "E",
        "answer": "E"
      }
    ],
    "head": "0"
  }
]